[Music]
tired of manually matching incoming
invoices to purchase orders even when
your system is set up to automatically
receive electronic documents tediously
matching line items is not how you want
to start your workday Microsoft copilot
and Dynamics 365 business Central does
the hard work so you don't have to using
powerful AI co-pilot analyzes the E
invoice and compares the line items with
your purchase order getting you to Green
in no time even even if you're dealing
with dozens or perhaps hundreds of lines
co-pilot also signals slight
discrepancies that are within the
tolerance levels that you
control and identifies line items that
may be split or grouped differently
after a quick review this invoice is
successfully mapped and ready to apply
to the purchase
order and business Central updates the
vendor document number and date so that
it's ready for
processing keep up with payables and
reclaim time for your most impactful
work with co-pilot in business Central